Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records Addendum WAG.124.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series XI: Files of the Research Department, 1947-1998
  - Council on Wage and Price Stability (IV), 1978-1980 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Council on Wage and Price Stability (V), 1978-1980 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Council on Wage and Price Stability: Evaluation of the Pay and Price Standards Program, Jan 16, 1981 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Data Requests by Av-Med Health Plan (I), 1986 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Data Requests by Av-Med Health Plan (II), 1986 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - Discrimination Grievance Study, 1986-1988 (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - Divestiture, 1985-1988 (Box 187, Folder 10)
  - Economic Policy, 1980 (Box 187, Folder 11)
  - Economic Policy, 1981 (Box 187, Folder 12)
  - Employee Educational Assistance, 1988 (Box 187, Folder 13)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: American Telephone and Telegraph (AT&T), 1947-1980 (Box 187, Folder 14)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Bell System General Department, 1947-1980 (Box 187, Folder 15)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Chesapeake and Potomac (C&P) Bell, 1947-1980 (Box 187, Folder 16)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: C&P Bell of Maryland, 1948-1980 (Box 187, Folder 17)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Chesapeake and Potomac (C&P) Bell of Virginia, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Chesapeake and Potomac (C&P) Bell of West Virginia, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Cincinnati Bell, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Diamond State Bell, 1948-1980 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Illinois Bell, 1947-1976 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Indiana Bell, 1947-1974 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Inter-Mountain Bell, 1947-1979 (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Longlines, 1948-1980 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Michigan Bell, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Mountain States Bell, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Nevada Bell, 1948-1980 (Box 188, Folder 11)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: New England Bell, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 12)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: New Jersey Bell, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 13)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: New York Bell, 1959-1980 (Box 188, Folder 14)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Northwestern Bell, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 15)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Ohio Bell, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 16)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Pacific Bell, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 17)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Pacific Northwest Bell, 1962-1980 (Box 188, Folder 18)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Pennsylvania Bell, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 19)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: South Central Bell, 1972-1980 (Box 188, Folder 20)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Southern Bell, 1948-1980 (Box 188, Folder 21)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Southern New England Bell, 1947-1980 (Box 188, Folder 22)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Southwestern Bell, 1948-1980 (Box 188, Folder 23)
  - Employee/Salary Reports: Wisconsin Bell, 1949-1980 (Box 188, Folder 24)
  - Employment Testing, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 25)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC) Report on Domestic Telecommunications Policy (I), Sep 27, 1976 (Box 188, Folder 26)
  - FCC Report on Domestic Telecommunications Policy (II), Sep 27, 1976 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service (FMCS) Conference, 1988 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Financial Analysis (I), 1988 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Financial Analysis (II), 1988 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - General Telephone Company (GTE) of California, 1988-1989 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Health Care, 1985 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Health Care Deregulation, Jul 1995 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Health Care Meeting, Jul 5, 1988-Jul 6, 1988 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Illinois Bell Agreement with CWA, Aug 10, 1986 (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - Illinois Bell: Bargaining and Health Plan, 1986 (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - Indiana Bell (I), 1986 (Box 189, Folder 11)
  - Indiana Bell (II), 1986 (Box 189, Folder 12)
  - International Business Machines (IBM): Directories/Locations, 1985 (Box 189, Folder 13)
  - IBM: International Conference, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 14)
  - IBM: On The Job, 1985-1987 (Box 189, Folder 15)
  - IBM: Wage Survey, 1986-1989 (Box 189, Folder 16)
  - Job Evaluation Advisory Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 189, Folder 17)
  - Job Evaluation Bargaining Chairmen, May 13, 1981-May 14, 1981 (Box 189, Folder 18)
  - Job Re-Design/Re-Engineering (I), 1994-1995 (Box 189, Folder 19)
  - Job Re-Design/Re-Engineering (II), 1994-1995 (Box 189, Folder 20)
  - Job Re-Design/Re-Engineering (III), 1994-1995 (Box 189, Folder 21)
  - Kaiser Health Care: Job Descriptions, 1993-1994 (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Kaiser-Permanente, 1988 (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Layoffs, 1985 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Local 1109, 1991-1992 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Lockheed (I), 1993-1998 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Lockheed (II), 1993-1997 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Maximus Incorporated, 1997-1998 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - MCI: Anti-Union Material, 1980-1986 (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - MCI: Average Salary Roster, Apr 1986 (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - MCI: Benefits, 1982-1985 (Box 190, Folder 10)
  - MCI: Contacts, 1986 (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - MCI: Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1985-1986 (Box 190, Folder 12)
  - MCI: Layoffs, 1986-1987 (Box 190, Folder 13)
  - MCI: Locations and Names Lists, 1986 (Box 190, Folder 14)
  - MCI: Newsletter Ideas-Wages, 1986 (Box 190, Folder 15)
  - MCI: Organizing, 1986 (Box 190, Folder 16)
  - MCI Presentation, 1988 (Box 190, Folder 17)
  - MCI Reports, 1985-1990 (Box 190, Folder 18)
  - MCI: Shareholder Action, 1986 (Box 190, Folder 19)
  - MCI: Wage per Hour Information, 1987-1988 (Box 190, Folder 20)
  - MCI: Washington, D.C.-19th Street Technicians, 1985 (Box 190, Folder 21)
  - MEP Claims/CAR Summaries (I), 1984 (Box 190, Folder 22)
  - MEP Claims/CAR Summaries (II), 1984 (Box 190, Folder 23)
  - Michigan Bell: Bargaining Book (I), 1989 (Box 190, Folder 24)
  - Michigan Bell: Bargaining Book (II), 1989 (Box 190, Folder 25)
  - Michigan Bell: Benefit Agreements, 1992 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Michigan Bell: Retiree Benefits, 1992 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Modernization, 1988 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Monitoring, 1986 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Multinational Corporation Information, 1987-1988 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - National Communications Union (NCU): United Kingdom, 1990-1993 (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - National Information Infrastructure (NII): Executive Council-Resource Publications, 1991-1992 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - NII: Executive Council-Resource Publications, 1993 (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - NII: Executive Council-Resource Publications (I), 1994 (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - NII: Executive Council-Resource Publications (II), 1994 (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - NII: Executive Council-Resource Publications, 1995 (Box 191, Folder 11)
  - NII: Executive Council-Resource Publications, 1996-1997 (Box 191, Folder 12)
  - NII: Job Training, 1997 (Box 191, Folder 13)
  - Navigating the New Health Care Environment, 1995 (Box 191, Folder 14)
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph: Blue Cross/Blue Shield Agreement, Jan 1, 1982 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph: John Hancock Insurance Agreement, Dec 1, 1957 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - New York Telephone and New England Telephone and Telegraph (NYNEX): Form 5500, 1983 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - NYNEX: Form 5500, 1984 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - NYNEX: Group Life Insurance, 1984-1985 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - NYNEX: Sickness and Disability, 1984-1986 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - NYNEX: Voluntary Income Protection Plan (VIPP), 1986 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Northern Telecom: Action Day, 1992 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Northern Telecom: Action Plan, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Northern Telecom: Alcatel Sale, 1993 (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Northern Telecom: American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1990-1991 (Box 192, Folder 11)
  - Northern Telecom: Analyst Reports, 1986-1990 (Box 192, Folder 12)
  - Northern Telecom: Anti-Union Strategy, 1986 (Box 192, Folder 13)
  - Northern Telecom: Barber Report, 1984-1986 (Box 192, Folder 14)
  - Northern Telecom: Board of Directors, 1990 (Box 192, Folder 15)
  - Northern Telecom: Brochure Printing, 1992 (Box 192, Folder 16)
  - Northern Telecom: Canadian Auto Workers (CAW), CWA, and Communications and Electrical Workers of Canada (CWC) Coalition, 1990 (Box 192, Folder 17)
  - Northern Telecom: CAW Contracts, 1979-1991 (Box 192, Folder 18)
  - Northern Telecom: CAW Report on Technological Change, 1988-1989 (Box 192, Folder 19)
  - Northern Telecom: Church Contacts, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 20)
  - Northern Telecom Clippings (I), 1991 (Box 192, Folder 21)
  - Northern Telecom: Clippings (II), 1991 (Box 192, Folder 22)
  - Northern Telecom: Coalition Conference Brochure, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 23)
  - Northern Telecom: Coalition Newsletter, Sep 7, 1993 (Box 192, Folder 24)
  - Northern Telecom: Cohen/Pomeroy Articles on Alliance, Undated (Box 192, Folder 25)
  - Northern Telecom: Committee for Economic Development, 1984-1986 (Box 192, Folder 26)
  - Northern Telecom: CWA Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 192, Folder 27)
  - Northern Telecom: CWA Local 1109, 1990 (Box 192, Folder 28)
  - Northern Telecom: CWA-Press on Toronto Conference, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 29)
  - Northern Telecom: CWA Strike, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 30)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Australia, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 31)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Austria, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 32)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Brazil, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 33)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Call Letter, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 34)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Country Reports, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 35)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Ireland, 1991-1992 (Box 192, Folder 36)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: List of Participants-Other Contacts, 1992 (Box 192, Folder 37)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Malaysia, 1988-1994 (Box 192, Folder 38)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Notes, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 39)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Overview Text, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Postal, Telephone and Telegraph International (PTTI), 1991-1992 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Press Coverage, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Press Releases, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: Sweden, 1990-1991 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: United Kingdom-Amalgamated Engineering Union (AEU), 1991 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: United Kingdom-Manufacturing, Science and Finance (MSF), 1991 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: United Kingdom-National Communications Union (NCU), 1991-1992 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: United Kingdom-Society of Telecom Executives (STE), 1991 (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: United Kingdom-Transport and General Workers Union (TGWU), 1991 (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Northern Telecom Conference: United States Invitations, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - Northern Telecom: Cross Border Links, 1992 (Box 193, Folder 12)
  - Northern Telecom: Dugan, John, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 13)
  - Northern Telecom: Electronic Monitoring Policy, Jan 30, 1992 (Box 193, Folder 14)
  - Northern Telecom: Employee Lists, 1989 (Box 193, Folder 15)
  - Northern Telecom: Excelsior Employee List, 1982 (Box 193, Folder 16)
  - Northern Telecom: France, 1992 (Box 193, Folder 17)
  - Northern Telecom: Hadley, Karen, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 18)
  - Northern Telecom: Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR), 1991 (Box 193, Folder 19)
  - Northern Telecom: International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU), 1991 (Box 193, Folder 20)
  - Northern Telecom: International Metalworkers Federation (IMF), 1991-1992 (Box 193, Folder 21)
  - Northern Telecom: International Petitions, 1992-1993 (Box 193, Folder 22)
  - Northern Telecom: International Solidarity Coalition, 1992-1994 (Box 193, Folder 23)
  - Northern Telecom: Lawsuit Settlement, 1992 (Box 193, Folder 24)
  - Northern Telecom: Lewis, Jim (Episcopal Reverend), 1991 (Box 193, Folder 25)
  - Northern Telecom: List of Unions, 1993 (Box 193, Folder 26)
  - Northern Telecom: McLaughlin, Audrey, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 27)
  - Northern Telecom: Minnetonka, MN, 1986 (Box 193, Folder 28)
  - Northern Telecom: Nashville, TN, 1977-1984 (Box 193, Folder 29)
  - Northern Telecom: Neutrality Statement, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 30)
  - Northern Telecom: NYNEX-Meridian Organization, 1992 (Box 193, Folder 31)
  - Northern Telecom: Organizing Prospectus, Undated (Box 193, Folder 32)
  - Northern Telecom: Organization Chart, Undated (Box 193, Folder 33)
  - Northern Telecom: Ownership, 1983 (Box 193, Folder 34)
  - Northern Telecom: Peres Report, 1989 (Box 193, Folder 35)
  - Northern Telecom: Petitions, 1992 (Box 193, Folder 36)
  - Northern Telecom: Poland, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 37)
  - Northern Telecom: Press, 1993 (Box 193, Folder 38)
  - Northern Telecom: Press Contacts, Undated (Box 193, Folder 39)
  - Northern Telecom: Raleigh Organizing, Jul 31, 1992 (Box 193, Folder 40)
  - Northern Telecom: Sample Brochures, 1989 (Box 193, Folder 41)
  - Northern Telecom: Solidarity Coalition, 1993 (Box 193, Folder 42)
  - Northern Telecom: Stockholder Resolutions, 1991-1992 (Box 193, Folder 43)
  - Northern Telecom: Strategy, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 44)
  - Northern Telecom: Szpack (AFL-CIO), 1991 (Box 193, Folder 45)
  - Northern Telecom: Toxic Chemical Release, 1990-1991 (Box 193, Folder 46)
  - Northern Telecom: Turkey, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 47)
  - Northern Telecom: United Auto Workers (UAW) Organizing, 1983-1984 (Box 193, Folder 48)
  - Northern Telecom: U.S. Organizing/Bargaining, 1982-1986 (Box 193, Folder 49)
  - Northern Telecom: Zendentsu Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 193, Folder 50)
  - Occupational Job Evaluation (OJE): American Telephone and Telegraph (AT&T) Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 193, Folder 51)
  - OJE: AT&T Committee Agendas, 1980-1982 (Box 193, Folder 52)
  - OJE: AT&T Committee Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 193, Folder 53)
  - OJE: AT&T Committee Mission Statement and Objectives, 1980 (Box 193, Folder 54)
  - OJE: Board Meeting, 1980-1981 (Box 193, Folder 55)
  - OJE Committee: Contract Language, 1980 (Box 193, Folder 56)
  - OJE: Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 193, Folder 57)
  - OJE: Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 193, Folder 58)
  - OJE: Definitions, Undated (Box 193, Folder 59)
  - OJE: Denver Pre-Test Questionnaire, Apr 9, 1981 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - OJE: Discussion with Ken Ross, Dec 4, 1980 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - OJE: Factors, Undated (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - OJE: Industrial and Labor Related Articles, 1981 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - OJE: Issues and AT&T Plan, Dec 1981 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - OJE: Job Descriptions-Denver, 1982-1983 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - OJE: Notes, Nov 1981 (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - OJE: Proposals (Originals), 1983 (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - OJE: Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 194, Folder 9)
  - OJE: Strike Paper, Undated (Box 194, Folder 10)
  - OJE: Systems Technician/Office Clerical Assistant Task Statement, 1981 (Box 194, Folder 11)
  - OJE: Training Session, Nov 1, 1981-Nov 13, 1981 (Box 194, Folder 12)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1980 (Box 194, Folder 13)
  - Occupational Safety and Health: Bargaining Proposals, 1977-1979 (Box 194, Folder 14)
  - Occupational Safety and Health: Video Display Terminals (VDT's), 1980-1981 (Box 194, Folder 15)
  - Ohio Bell (I), 1986 (Box 194, Folder 16)
  - Ohio Bell (II), 1986 (Box 194, Folder 17)
  - Ohio Bell: Business Structures, 1989 (Box 194, Folder 18)
  - Ohio Bell: Health Care Summary Plan Descriptions, 1983-1984 (Box 194, Folder 19)
  - Operator Take-Back, 1986 (Box 194, Folder 20)
  - Outsourcing: Information Technology, 1997 (Box 194, Folder 21)
  - Pacific Bell: Occupational Job Evaluation (OJE), 1988 (Box 194, Folder 22)
  - Pacific Northwest Bell: Bargaining Data (I), 1986 (Box 194, Folder 23)
  - Pacific Northwest Bell: Bargaining Data (II), 1986 (Box 194, Folder 24)
  - Pacific Telecom Annual Report, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 25)
  - Pacific Telesis Binder (I), 1989 (Box 194, Folder 26)
  - Pacific Telesis Binder (II), 1989 (Box 194, Folder 27)
  - Pacific Telesis Negotiations, 1989 (Box 194, Folder 28)
  - Pacific Telesis Pension Plan, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 29)
  - Pacific Telesis: Response to the National Telecommunications and Information Administration, 1985 (Box 194, Folder 30)
  - Pacific Telesis Settlement, 1988 (Box 194, Folder 31)
  - Postal, Telephone and Telegraph International (PTTI): International Business Machines (IBM), 1987 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Preparing for Negotiations and Costing the Contract, Undated (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Productivity Study: Chinoy, 1980 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Quality of Work Life (QWL): ATTCOM, 1985-1986 (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - QWL: ATT-Tech, 1986 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - QWL: Ameritech, 1985-1986 (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - QWL: Bell Labs, Undated (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - QWL: Bell South, 1986 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - QWL: Connecticut Conference, Jun 6, 1985-Jun 7, 1985 (Box 195, Folder 9)
  - QWL: Illinois Bell, 1985 (Box 195, Folder 10)
  - QWL: Kansas City Works, 1985 (Box 195, Folder 11)
  - QWL: Meeting-Richmond, VA, 1983 (Box 195, Folder 12)
  - QWL: Merrick Valley Works, 1984-1985 (Box 195, Folder 13)
  - QWL: Mountain Bell, 1986 (Box 195, Folder 14)
  - QWL: New York Telephone, 1984 (Box 195, Folder 15)
  - QWL: Ohio Bell, 1985 (Box 195, Folder 16)
  - QWL: Pacific Bell, 1986-1987 (Box 195, Folder 17)
  - QWL: Pacific Northwest Bell, 1985 (Box 195, Folder 18)
  - QWL: Resource Committee Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 195, Folder 19)
  - QWL: Resource Meeting Packet, 1982 (Box 195, Folder 20)
  - QWL: Resource Training Book, Mar 22, 1982-Mar 25, 1982 (Box 195, Folder 21)
  - QWL: Resource Training Materials, 1981-1982 (Box 195, Folder 22)
  - QWL: Southwest Bell, 1984-1986 (Box 195, Folder 23)
  - QWL: Survey of Steering Committee Co-Chairs-1982 Activities and 1983 Goals (Box 195, Folder 24)
  - QWL: The Role of Third Parties in Labor-Management Cooperative Endeavors, 1978 (Box 195, Folder 25)
  - QWL: Wisconsin Bell, 1987 (Box 195, Folder 26)
  - Real Wage Insurance, 1978-1979 (Box 195, Folder 27)
  - Safety and Advisory Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 195, Folder 28)
  - Smoke-Free Workplace, 1980 (Box 195, Folder 29)
  - South Central Bell Agreement, Aug 8, 1986 (Box 195, Folder 30)
  - Southern Bell Agreement, Aug 9, 1986 (Box 195, Folder 31)
  - Southwest Bell: Bargaining (I), 1989 (Box 195, Folder 32)
  - Southwest Bell: Bargaining (II), 1989 (Box 195, Folder 33)
  - Southwest Bell: Bargaining Focus, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 34)
  - Southwest Bell: Data Requests (I), 1989 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Southwest Bell: Data Requests (II), 1989 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Southwest Bell: Data Requests (III), 1989 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - Southwest Bell: Pension, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Southwest Bell: Pre-Bargaining Presentation, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - Speeches, Remarks, Reviews, Manuals and Studies, 1984 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - State Regulation: Interconnection, 1997 (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - Stress Study Correspondence, 1981 (Box 196, Folder 8)
  - Strike Articles (I), 1989 (Box 196, Folder 9)
  - Strike Articles (II), 1989 (Box 196, Folder 10)
  - Strike Articles (III), 1989 (Box 196, Folder 11)
  - Switched Access Remote Test System (SARTS), 1982 (Box 196, Folder 12)
  - Technology: Arbitration Cases, 1974-1985 (Box 196, Folder 13)
  - Technology: Case Studies, 1980 (Box 196, Folder 14)
  - Technology: Change, 1984 (Box 196, Folder 15)
  - Technology: Jobs, 1984-1990 (Box 196, Folder 16)
  - Technology: Mechanized Accounts Payable System (MAPS) (I), 1993 (Box 196, Folder 17)
  - Technology: Mechanized Accounts Payable System (MAPS) (II), 1993 (Box 196, Folder 18)
  - Technology: National and Local Government Officers (NALGO) Negotiators Guide, 1980 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Technology: New Technology and Collective Bargaining, 1981 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Technology: Stewards Project, 1986 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - Technology: Telephone Operators, 1984-1988 (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - Technology: Training-Bernard, Elaine, 1986 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - Technology: Working Women, 1983 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Training Advisory Board Meeting, Sep 7, 1984 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - Union of Communications Workers (UCW): United Kingdom, 1991 (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - Unisys Fraud Case, 1997 (Box 197, Folder 9)
  - Universal Service: Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 197, Folder 10)
  - Universal Service: Resource Oublications, 1993-1996 (Box 197, Folder 11)
  - Wage-Price Guidelines (I), 1978-1980 (Box 197, Folder 12)
  - Wage-Price Guidelines (II), 1978-1980 (Box 197, Folder 13)
  - Wage-Price Guidelines (III), 1978-1980 (Box 197, Folder 14)
  - Wage-Price Guidelines (IV), 1978-1980 (Box 197, Folder 15)
  - Watts, Glenn E.: Speech to American Productivity Center, Oct 1984 (Box 197, Folder 16)
  - Waynesboro-Covington-Clifton Forge (WWCF) Association of Independent Telephone Workers, 1987 (Box 197, Folder 17)
  - Welfare Privatization (I), 1996-1997 (Box 197, Folder 18)
  - Welfare Privatization (II), 1996-1997 (Box 197, Folder 19)
  - Western Electric: Final Settlement, 1983 (Box 197, Folder 20)
  - Western Electric: Form 5500, undated (Box 197, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration Case Guide, 1957-1998 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - 3 boxes of microfiche, 1957-1998 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - 3 boxes of microfiche, 1957-1998 (Box 199, Folder 1)